<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TakeAHike2</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Info Page -->
    <string name="infoDesc">Maps have suggested ability descriptors. Shenandoah\'s Hiking Difficulty is determined by a numerical rating using the following formula:</string>
    <string name="difficultyTitle">Hiking Difficulty</string>
    <string name="hikeExample">Elevation Gain x 2 x distance (in miles). The product\'s square root is the numerical rating.
                    For example, a 10-mile hike that gains 2,200 feet in elevation:
                    \n2,200 x 2=4,400
                    \n4,400 x 10 = 44,000
                    \nSquare root of 44,000=209.8</string>
    <string name="descCont">The hike\'s numerical rating is then tied to one of five descriptors: Easiest, Moderate, Moderately Strenuous, Strenuous, Very Strenuous.
                    \nThe example hike (above) would be rated Very Strenuous.
                    \nThere are a few exceptions to the formula\'s validity, such as Dark Hollow Falls. Although its numeric rating of 36.3 puts it in the \"Easiest\" range,
                    its steepness over such a short distance warrants a \"Moderate.\"</string>
    <string name="easiestTitle">Easiest</string>
    <string name="easiestDesc">Numerical Rating: less than 50
                    \nA hike that is generally suitable for anyone who enjoys walking. Mostly level or with a slight incline. Generally less than 3 miles.</string>
    <string name="moderateTitle">Moderate</string>
    <string name="moderateDesc">Numerical Rating: 50-100
                    \nA moderate hike is generally suitable for novice hikers who want a bit of a challenge. The terrain will involve a moderate incline and may have some steeper sections. Generally 3 to 5 miles.</string>
    <string name="moderateStrenTitle">Moderately Strenuous</string>
    <string name="moderateStrenDesc">Numerical Rating: 100–150
                    \nModerately Strenuous hikes will generally be challenging for an unconditioned person. The terrain will involve a steady and often steep incline. Generally 5 to 8 miles.</string>
    <string name="strenuousTitle">Strenuous</string>
    <string name="strenuousDesc">Numerical Rating: 150-200
                    \nStrenuous hikes will challenge most hikers. The hike will generally be longer and steeper, but may be deemed "Strenuous" because of the elevation gain. Generally 7 to 10 miles.</string>
    <string name="veryStrenuousTitle">Very Strenuous</string>
    <string name="veryStrenuousDesc">Numerical Rating : greater than 200
                    \nOnly well-conditioned and well-prepared hikers should attempt very strenuous hikes.
                    The hike will generally be long and steep, and may include rock scrambling, stream crossings, and other challenging terrain. Generally 8 miles and over.</string>
    <string name="avgPaceTitle">Average Pace is:</string>
    <string name="avgPaceDesc">1.5 miles per hour for easiest trails.
                    \n1.4 mph for moderate trails.
                    \n1.3 mph for moderately strenuous trails.
                    \n1.2 mph for strenuous and very strenuous trails.
                    \nThis is hiking time and does not take into consideration fitness, exploration, rest, contemplation, etc.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_started__hike">Started_Hike</string>

    <string name="title_activity_hike__started">Hike_Started</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
</resources>
